♪I've braved the storms, walked through the rain♪
لقد تحديت العواصف، وسرت تحت المطر
♪Seen the highs and lows along the way♪
♪لقد رأيت الارتفاعات والانخفاضات على طول الطريق♪
♪But you stay quiet, never change♪
♪لكنك تبقى هادئًا، ولا تتغير أبدًا♪
♪Like a child who dreams beneath the stars♪
♪مثل طفل يحلم تحت النجوم♪
♪I've read the story in your eyes♪
♪لقد قرأت القصة في عينيك♪
♪And finally, nothing's left to hide♪
♪وأخيرًا، لم يعد هناك ما نخفيه♪
♪You won't give in to a world so cold♪
♪لن تستسلم لعالم بارد جدًا♪
♪So you wander through it on your own♪
♪لذا تتجول فيه بمفردك♪
♪Maybe fate has drawn us near♪
ربما يكون القدر قد قربنا
♪Just to help you learn to believe♪
♪فقط لمساعدتك على تعلم الإيمان♪
♪Everything you've questioned deep inside♪
♪كل ما تساءلت عنه في أعماقك♪
♪I'll be the proof you need♪
♪سأكون الدليل الذي تحتاجه♪
♪I've made my choice♪
♪لقد اتخذت قراري♪
♪For you, I'll be brave and break the rules♪
♪من أجلك، سأكون شجاعًا وأكسر القواعد♪
♪What's there to fear even if the world is right and I am wrong?♪
♪ما الذي يجب أن تخاف منه حتى لو كان العالم على حق وأنا على خطأ؟♪
♪One day, all of this will turn into memories♪
♪في يوم من الأيام، كل هذا سوف يتحول إلى ذكريات♪
♪Every storm we faced will turn into our life's scenery♪
♪كل عاصفة نواجهها سوف تتحول إلى مشهد حياتنا♪
♪For you, I'll be brave and break the rules♪
♪من أجلك، سأكون شجاعًا وأكسر القواعد♪
♪What's there to fear even if the world is right and I am wrong?♪
♪ما الذي يجب أن تخاف منه حتى لو كان العالم على حق وأنا على خطأ؟♪
♪Even if, in the end, the whole world turns against me♪
♪حتى لو تحول العالم كله ضدي في النهاية♪
♪I won't regret having loved you♪
♪لن أندم على حبي لك♪
♪With all my heart♪
♪من كل قلبي♪
♪I've held you close♪
لقد احتضنتك بقوة
♪Walked by your side♪
♪مشيت بجانبك♪
♪And loved the fire that burned inside you♪
♪وأحببت النار التي احترقت بداخلك♪
[The First Frost]
[الصقيع الأول]
[Adapted from the novel of the same name by Zhu Yi]
[مقتبس من رواية تحمل نفس الاسم بقلم تشو يي]
Sang Yan fought another student
سانج يان قاتل طالبًا آخر
for Wen Yifan.
لـ وين ييفان.
As for the fight
أما بالنسبة للقتال
we've already settled it
لقد قمنا بتسوية الأمر بالفعل
with the injured student.
مع الطالب المصاب
Now, what we need to handle
الآن، ما الذي نحتاج إلى التعامل معه؟
is the issue of your early romance.
هي مسألة رومانسيتك المبكرة.
We're not in a relationship.
نحن لسنا في علاقة.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
We're not in an early relationship.
نحن لسنا في علاقة مبكرة.
My feelings for Wen Yifan
مشاعري تجاه وين ييفان
are one-sided.
هي من جانب واحد.
Teenagers often have fantasies about love.
في كثير من الأحيان يكون لدى المراهقين تخيلات حول الحب.
I understand that.
انا أفهم ذلك.
But you have such heavy schoolwork now.
لكن لديك واجبات مدرسية ثقيلة الآن.
You'll definitely get distracted by early romance.
سوف تشتت انتباهك بالتأكيد بالرومانسية المبكرة.
Sang Yan
سانج يان
can you turn your passion
هل تستطيع تحويل شغفك
into motivation for hard work?
إلى التحفيز للعمل الجاد؟
You'll mature in university
سوف تنضج في الجامعة
and there's plenty of time for dating then.
وهناك الكثير من الوقت للمواعدة إذن.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Yes.
نعم.
Yifan's uncle
عم ييفان
you really should pay more attention.
ينبغي عليك حقا أن تولي المزيد من الاهتمام.
You should care more about her.
ينبغي عليك الاهتمام بها أكثر.
Okay.
تمام.
Alright, it's no big deal.
حسنًا، إنها ليست مشكلة كبيرة.
You can communicate.
يمكنك التواصل.
That's it.
هذا كل شيء.
I'm off to class.
سأذهب إلى الفصل.
Stand properly.
قف بشكل صحيح.
The teacher was explaining so well!
لقد كان المعلم يشرح بشكل جيد للغاية!
Thank you, teacher.
شكرا لك يا معلم.
Have some shame.
اشعر ببعض الخجل.
How can you be so shameless?
كيف يمكنك أن تكون وقحًا إلى هذه الدرجة؟
At such a young age
في مثل هذا العمر الصغير
you've already learned how to seduce men?
هل تعلمت بالفعل كيفية إغواء الرجال؟
You need to focus on your studies!
يجب عليك التركيز على دراستك!
You...
أنت...
You startled me.
لقد فاجأتني.
You really like her?
هل تحبها حقا؟
Is that even a question?
هل هذا سؤال حقا؟
Son, well done.
ابني، أحسنت.
Good taste.
ذوق جيد.
You've got the same taste as me.
لديك نفس الذوق مثلي.
Even if you like her, just bear with it.
حتى لو كنت تحبها، فقط تحملها.
Wait until university, okay?
انتظر حتى الجامعة، حسنًا؟
Right.
يمين.
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
Go home!
إذهب إلى المنزل!
Go home and pack your things!
اذهب إلى المنزل وحزم أغراضك!
Did you hear me?
هل سمعتني؟
Why do I need to pack my things?
لماذا أحتاج إلى حزم أغراضي؟
Well, your aunt's brother
حسنًا، شقيق عمتك
has a house in Beiyu.
لديه منزل في بيو.
We're planning to move there.
نحن نخطط للانتقال إلى هناك.
Listen
يستمع
after transferring schools
بعد نقل المدارس
you have to completely sever ties
يجب عليك قطع العلاقات تماما
with this guy!
مع هذا الرجل!
Did you hear me?
هل سمعتني؟
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
[Episode 7] [A Secret...]
[الحلقة 7] [سر...]
[3085 Days]
[3085 يوما]
[Cutting Room]
[غرفة القطع]
[23rd Day of Living Together Officially]
[اليوم الثالث والعشرون للعيش معًا رسميًا]
[Sang Yan]
[سانغ يان]
What time are you on duty until?
حتى متى أنت في الخدمة؟
[Wen Yifan]
[وين ييفان]
I'm about to finish work.
أنا على وشك الانتهاء من العمل.
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
[Sang Yan]
[سانغ يان]
Could you help me pick up a pizza on your way?
هل بإمكانك مساعدتي في شراء البيتزا في طريقك؟
Someone wants it.
أحدهم يريد ذلك.
Why doesn't he just order takeout?
لماذا لا يطلب الطعام الجاهز؟
Eating pizza during the New Year?
أكل البيتزا في رأس السنة الجديدة؟
Is it because his girlfriend wants it?
هل هذا لأن صديقته تريد ذلك؟
Pick your favorite flavor.
اختر نكهتك المفضلة.
Isn't what you're doing a bit scummy?
أليس ما تفعله أمرًا حقيرًا بعض الشيء؟
[Pizza Hut]
[بيتزا هت]
Why are so many people
لماذا يوجد الكثير من الناس
eating pizza during the New Year holiday?
أكل البيتزا في عطلة رأس السنة الجديدة؟
Why isn't it Duan Jiaxu?
لماذا ليس دوان جياكسو؟
There's no Duan Jiaxu here.
لا يوجد دوان جياكسو هنا.
This is my roommate.
هذا هو زميلي في الغرفة.
Roommate?
رفيق السكن؟
Female roommate?
زميلة السكن أنثى؟
You two are sleeping together?
هل أنتم تنامون معًا؟
We live in two rooms...
نحن نعيش في غرفتين...
We live in two rooms.
نحن نعيش في غرفتين.
We just share this apartment.
نحن نتشارك هذه الشقة فقط.
I knew it!
كنت أعرف!
You're so pretty
أنت جميلة جدا
and my brother's so ugly.
وأخي قبيح جداً
You two could only be ordinary roommates.
لا يمكن أن تكونا سوى زميلين عاديين في السكن.
Miss, my name is Sang Zhi.
آنستي، اسمي سانغ تشي.
I'm his sister.
أنا أخته.
My name is Wen Yifan.
اسمي وين ييفان.
Miss, let me do it.
آنستي، دعيني أفعل ذلك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Sorry for the trouble.
عذرا على الإزعاج.
My mom won't let me eat Pizza at home.
أمي لن تسمح لي بتناول البيتزا في المنزل.
So I had to come here to satisfy my cravings.
لذلك كان علي أن آتي إلى هنا لإشباع رغباتي.
Who eats pizza during the New Year holiday?
من يأكل البيتزا في عطلة رأس السنة الجديدة؟
Mind your business.
اهتم بأمورك.
There really are a lot of people.
هناك حقا الكثير من الناس.
I waited half an hour to get this.
انتظرت نصف ساعة للحصول على هذا.
Eat up.
تناول الطعام.
After you're done, go study.
بعد الانتهاء، اذهب للدراسة.
You're still studying during the New Year holiday?
هل مازلت تدرس خلال عطلة رأس السنة الجديدة؟
I'm in my senior year.
أنا في سنتي الأخيرة.
You came here because it was too noisy to study at home
لقد أتيت إلى هنا لأن الدراسة في المنزل كانت صاخبة للغاية
with all the relatives around?
مع كل الأقارب حولك؟
What relatives?
ما هي الأقارب؟
It's very quiet at home.
إنه هادئ جداً في المنزل.
It's just me and my parents at home.
أنا ووالداي فقط في المنزل.
My brother's not coming back.
أخي لن يعود
It feels pretty lonely.
أشعر بالوحدة الشديدة.
Shouldn't you be back after the 8th day of New Year?
ألا يجب عليك أن تعود بعد اليوم الثامن من العام الجديد؟
There are too many relatives at home.
هناك الكثير من الأقارب في المنزل.
We don't have enough room.
ليس لدينا مساحة كافية.
Miss
يفتقد
were you my brother's classmate...
هل كنت زميلا لأخي؟
in high school?
في المدرسة الثانوية؟
Do you remember me?
هل تتذكرني؟
Of course I remember.
بالطبع أتذكر.
You're the prettiest
أنت الأجمل
of my brother's female classmates.
من زميلات أخي في الدراسة.
I was just focusing on food earlier
كنت أركز فقط على الطعام في وقت سابق
and didn't recognize you immediately.
ولم يتعرف عليك فورًا.
You're getting prettier too.
أنت تصبحين أجمل أيضاً.
Miss, do you remember me?
آنستي هل تتذكريني؟
Yes.
نعم.
Do you remember?
هل تذكر؟
When you were very young
عندما كنت صغيرا جدا
you once got lost?
هل ضللت طريقك مرة؟
Later, you asked me to help you find your brother.
طلبت مني لاحقًا أن أساعدك في العثور على أخيك.
You even promised to treat me to ice cream.
لقد وعدتني أيضًا بأن تتناول لي الآيس كريم.
Oh, I remember.
أوه، أتذكر.
I didn't get lost at that time.
لم أضيع في تلك اللحظة.
But my brother said I was lost
لكن أخي قال أنني ضائع
so I had to be lost.
لذلك كان علي أن أضيع.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Miss
يفتقد
I can't find my brother.
لا أستطيع العثور على أخي.
Is your brother
هل أخوك؟
from our school?
من مدرستنا؟
Yes.
نعم.
He asked me to wait for him at the overpass.
طلب مني أن أنتظره عند الجسر.
The overpass...
الجسر العلوي...
is over there.
هو هناك.
I'll take you there.
سأأخذك إلى هناك.
Thank you, Miss.
شكرا لك يا آنسة.
Do you remember your brother's phone number?
هل تتذكر رقم هاتف أخيك؟
I don't remember it.
لا أتذكره.
What does your brother look like?
كيف يبدو أخوك؟
He...
هو...
is really handsome.
إنه وسيم حقا.
Everyone likes to play with him.
الجميع يحب اللعب معه.
Which one is your brother?
من هو أخوك؟
That one over there.
هذا الذي هناك.
Didn't I tell you to wait for me here?
ألم أخبرك أن تنتظرني هنا؟
How would I know this place?
كيف يمكنني أن أعرف هذا المكان؟
What a coincidence.
يا لها من مصادفة!
She's my sister.
إنها أختي.
I'm going now.
سأذهب الآن.
Miss, thank you.
شكرا لك سيدتي.
Let's eat ice cream together.
دعونا نأكل الآيس كريم معًا.
If you're free, let's go.
إذا كنت حرًا، دعنا نذهب.
If it weren't for my brother's promise to buy me candy
لو لم يكن هناك وعد من أخي بشراء الحلوى لي
I wouldn't have helped him...
لن أساعده...
I wouldn't have helped him lie.
لن أساعده على الكذب.
Let's go, Miss.
دعنا نذهب يا آنسة.
Let's go eat pizza.
دعنا نذهب لتناول البيتزا.
I'm not hungry.
أنا لست جائعا.
You guys go ahead.
تفضلوا يا شباب.
By the way
بالمناسبة
there's a lot of food
هناك الكثير من الطعام
in these cabinets
في هذه الخزائن
and in the fridge.
وفي الثلاجة.
Take whatever you want.
خذ ما تريد.
It's mostly your brother's stuff.
إنها في الغالب أشياء أخيك.
Wait, Miss.
انتظري يا آنسة.
How did you end up as my brother's roommate?
كيف انتهى بك الأمر كزميل سكن لأخي؟
Just a coincidence.
مجرد مصادفة.
It must be fate.
لا بد أن يكون هذا القدر.
Are you eating or not?
هل تأكل أم لا؟
Hurry up, go eat.
اسرع، اذهب لتناول الطعام.
I'm going to work now.
سأذهب للعمل الآن.
You're such a bigmouth.
أنت شخص ثرثار للغاية.
It's time to eat!
حان وقت الأكل!
Go bring the other dishes over.
اذهب واحضر باقي الأطباق.
Why don't you ask Yifan to join us for dinner?
لماذا لا تطلب من ييفان الانضمام إلينا لتناول العشاء؟
Aren't you going to invite her?
ألا تنوي دعوتها؟
Since you two are roommates
بما أنكما زميلان في السكن
you should get along well.
ينبغي أن تتوافقوا بشكل جيد.
Why are you talking like mom?
لماذا تتحدث مثل أمي؟
Besides, what's it got to do with you?
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، ما علاقة هذا الأمر بك؟
She's been good to me.
لقد كانت جيدة معي.
She even lets me take whatever I want.
حتى أنها تسمح لي بأخذ ما أريد.
Shouldn't you be polite with her?
ألا ينبغي عليك أن تكون مهذبا معها؟
She's nice to you
إنها لطيفة معك
but what's it got to do with me?
ولكن ما علاقة هذا بي؟
Invite her yourself.
ادعوها بنفسك.
I won't.
أنا لن.
She's not my roommate, anyway.
إنها ليست زميلتي في الغرفة، على أية حال.
I'm not polite, and you shouldn't be either.
أنا لست مهذبًا، ولا ينبغي لك أن تكون كذلك أيضًا.
Go.
يذهب.
Miss Yifan.
Miss Yifan.
Please come in.
من فضلك ادخل.
Miss
يفتقد
my brother made a hotpot.
لقد صنع أخي وعاءًا ساخنًا.
Come join us.
تعال وانضم إلينا.
I'm not hungry. You guys go ahead.
أنا لست جائعًا، هيا يا رفاق.
Miss, you might not know
سيدتي، ربما لا تعرفين
but my brother and I
لكن أنا وأخي
can never enjoy a meal alone.
لا يمكن أبدًا الاستمتاع بتناول وجبة طعام بمفردك.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Okay.
تمام.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Are you hungry again so soon?
هل تشعر بالجوع مرة أخرى بهذه السرعة؟
My brother says
يقول أخي
the New Year is all about family reunion, having hotpot.
كل ما يتعلق بالعام الجديد هو لم شمل الأسرة وتناول الطعام الساخن.
Miss Yifan, please sit here.
آنسة ييفان، من فضلك اجلس هنا.
Thank you, Sang Zhi.
شكرا لك، سانغ تشي.
You can call me by my nickname, Zhi.
يمكنك أن تناديني باسمي المستعار، تشي.
Zhi?
تشي؟
That's really cute.
هذا لطيف حقا.
What are you laughing at?
على ماذا تضحك؟
What's wrong with her saying my nickname is cute?
ما المشكلة في قولها أن لقبي لطيف؟
Doesn't it sound like a maid's name?
ألا يبدو هذا مثل اسم الخادمة؟
Your name sounds like a eunuch.
اسمك يبدو مثل اسم الخصي.
You'd better say that in front of your dad.
من الأفضل أن تقول ذلك أمام والدك.
Eunuch Yan.
الخصي يان.
By the way, Zhi
بالمناسبة، تشي
you're about to take the university entrance exam, right?
أنت على وشك اجتياز امتحان القبول بالجامعة، أليس كذلك؟
Have you decided which university you want to go to?
هل قررت أي جامعة تريد الذهاب إليها؟
Not yet.
ليس بعد.
I'm stuck between Nanwu University and Yihe University.
أنا عالق بين جامعة نانوو وجامعة ييهي.
Are you confident about both?
هل أنت واثق من كليهما؟
Unless something unexpected happens.
ما لم يحدث أمر غير متوقع.
So, your grades are good enough.
إذن، درجاتك جيدة بما فيه الكفاية.
I'm just worried about a bad performance on the exam.
أنا فقط قلق بشأن الأداء السيئ في الامتحان.
No need to worry so much.
لا داعي للقلق كثيرا.
And both universities
وكلا الجامعتين
are pretty good.
جيدة جدًا.
They each have their own advantages.
لكل منهم مميزاته الخاصة.
The only thing is that Yihe is further from Nanwu.
الشيء الوحيد هو أن ييهي أبعد عن نانوو.
Also, the climate there is different from here.
كما أن المناخ هناك يختلف عن هنا.
You should consider this point.
ينبغي عليك أن تأخذ هذه النقطة في الاعتبار.
Miss, which university did you graduate from?
آنستي من أي جامعة تخرجت؟
Yihe University.
جامعة ييهي.
No wonder you know so much about it.
لا عجب أنك تعرف الكثير عنه.
What's your major?
ما هو تخصصك؟
Network and New Media.
الشبكات والإعلام الجديد.
Wouldn't Nanwu University be a better choice
ألا تعتبر جامعة نانوو خيارًا أفضل؟
for this major?
لهذا التخصص؟
If we just talk about this major
إذا تحدثنا فقط عن هذا الأمر الرئيسي
actually
في الحقيقة
Nanwu University's is the better choice.
جامعة نانوو هي الخيار الأفضل.
Then why did you choose Yihe University?
إذن لماذا اخترت جامعة ييهي؟
What are you looking at me for?
لماذا تنظر إلي؟
Keep talking.
استمر بالتحدث.
I want to know, too.
أريد أن أعرف أيضاً
What's the reason?
ما هو السبب؟
At that time, I didn't plan to apply for this major.
في ذلك الوقت، لم أكن أخطط للتقدم لهذا التخصص.
Maybe
ربما
I misjudged
لقد اخطأت في الحكم
the cut-off scores
الدرجات المقطوعة
so I applied to Yihe University.
لذلك تقدمت بطلب إلى جامعة ييهي.
I'm full.
أنا ممتلئة.
What's wrong with him?
ما خطبه؟
Why is he being so sarcastic?
لماذا هو ساخر هكذا؟
By the way, Yifan
بالمناسبة، ييفان
can I ask you something?
هل يمكننى ان اسألك شيئا؟
Did you
هل فعلت؟
ever date my brother?
هل تواعد أخي أبدًا؟
No.
لا.
I heard from my parents
سمعت من والدي
that my brother had an early romance
أن أخي كان له علاقة رومانسية مبكرة
in high school.
في المدرسة الثانوية.
I just remembered.
لقد تذكرت للتو.
Little rascal.
الوغد الصغير.
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
Let's go home.
دعنا نذهب إلى المنزل.
I just started eating.
لقد بدأت للتو في الأكل.
I want to stay a bit longer.
أريد البقاء لفترة أطول قليلاً.
Mom and Dad will be home soon.
أمي وأبي سوف يكونون في المنزل قريبا.
They asked me to escort you back.
لقد طلبوا مني مرافقتك مرة أخرى.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
No, I want to eat more.
لا، أريد أن آكل أكثر.
Eat? Who can eat more than you?
أكل؟ من يستطيع أن يأكل أكثر منك؟
What are you staring at?
ماذا تنظر اليه؟
Sang Yan, why do I feel
سانج يان، لماذا أشعر؟
like you don't treat Miss Yifan well?
كأنك لا تعامل الآنسة ييفان بشكل جيد؟
She's nice, isn't she?
إنها لطيفة، أليس كذلك؟
She's gentle when she talks.
إنها لطيفة عندما تتحدث.
But just based on apparences
ولكن فقط على أساس المظاهر
you two are worlds apart.
أنتم الاثنان عالمان مختلفان.
With your attitude
مع موقفك
girls definitely won't like it.
الفتيات بالتأكيد لن يعجبهن ذلك.
What attitude?
ما هو الموقف؟
Girls generally like
الفتيات عمومًا يحبون
gentle
لطيف
good-tempered
حسن الطباع
attentive
منتبه
and considerate guys.
ورجال متفهمون.
It's fine if their family situation isn't great.
لا بأس إذا لم يكن وضعهم العائلي ممتازًا.
Like Jiaxu.
مثل جياكسو.
Who?
من؟
Jiaxu.
جياكسو.
You're quite knowledgeable, huh?
أنت على دراية كبيرة، أليس كذلك؟
So
لذا
since you don't have the advantage in looks
لأنك لا تتمتع بميزة المظهر
you need to work harder.
يجب عليك أن تعمل بجدية أكبر.
Don't just stay at home
لا تكتفي بالبقاء في المنزل
sitting around.
الجلوس حول.
Does your brother have any other job
هل لدى أخيك أي عمل آخر؟
besides running the restaurant?
بالإضافة إلى إدارة المطعم؟
He did before
لقد فعل ذلك من قبل
but recently, I don't know why, he quit.
لكن مؤخرًا، لا أعلم السبب، فقد استقال.
Do you also think
هل تعتقد أيضا
my brother is a bit idle?
أخي خامل بعض الشيء؟
Today, she even asked me
واليوم حتى سألتني
about your work.
عن عملك.
Why don't you stop at the parking lot?
لماذا لا تتوقف عند موقف السيارات؟
It's just a few steps.
إنها مجرد بضع خطوات.
You can go up by yourself.
يمكنك الصعود بمفردك.
You're not going home tonight?
أنت لن تذهب إلى المنزل الليلة؟
Aren't you afraid Mom and Dad will break your legs?
ألا تخاف من أن يكسر أمك وأبوك ساقيك؟
Let me know when you're home.
أخبرني عندما تكون في المنزل.
Transfer the fare to me.
تحويل الأجرة لي.
Leaving?
مغادرة؟
I knew you had something going on!
لقد عرفت أن هناك شيئا يحدث!
♪The dust of lies and your wounds♪
♪غبار الأكاذيب وجراحك♪
♪All hide in your eyes♪
♪كل شيء يختبئ في عينيك♪
♪Jot down the wishes you've made before♪
♪اكتب الأمنيات التي تمنيتها من قبل♪
♪Will you cherish my heart...♪
♪هل ستعتز بقلبي...♪
You didn't go home?
لم تذهب إلى المنزل؟
It's too noisy at home.
إنه صاخب جدًا في المنزل.
Could it be noisier than here?
هل يمكن أن يكون أكثر ضجيجا من هنا؟
When I was little, I loved fireworks.
عندما كنت صغيرًا، كنت أحب الألعاب النارية.
Does your family set off fireworks for the New Year?
هل تقوم عائلتك بإطلاق الألعاب النارية احتفالاً بالعام الجديد؟
Not often.
ليس في كثير من الأحيان.
What about your sister? Doesn't she?
ماذا عن أختك؟ أليس كذلك؟
I don't focus on her much.
أنا لا أركز عليها كثيرا.
♪Can you hold me in your freezing night...♪
هل يمكنك أن تحتضني في ليلتك الباردة...؟
You didn't eat much earlier.
لم تأكل كثيرا في وقت سابق.
Are you hungry?
هل أنت جائع؟
If you're hungry
إذا كنت جائعا
we can cook...
نحن نستطيع الطبخ...
noodles.
معكرونة.
Are you going to cook a whole package again?
هل ستقوم بطبخ الحزمة بأكملها مرة أخرى؟
They look so happy over there.
يبدو أنهم سعداء جدًا هناك.
♪Fate changes and the confessions come too late♪
♪يتغير القدر وتأتي الاعترافات متأخرة جدًا♪
♪The love that was once absent...♪
♪الحب الذي كان غائبا ذات يوم...♪
[Fifteenth of January, Lantern Festival]
[الخامس عشر من يناير، مهرجان الفوانيس]
Just a reminder.
مجرد تذكير.
In a moment
في لحظة
eat more, talk less.
أكل أكثر، تحدث أقل.
You got it wrong.
لقد أخطأت.
What grandparents like
ما يحبه الأجداد
a granddaughter-in-law who eats in silence?
حفيدة ابنها تأكل في صمت؟
I'm afraid you'll spill the beans.
أخشى أنك سوف تكشف الحقيقة.
After all, my grandparents
بعد كل شيء، أجدادي
aren't just ordinary elderly.
ليسوا مجرد كبار السن العاديين.
How so?
كيف ذلك؟
Back then, to chase my grandma
في ذلك الوقت، لمطاردة جدتي
my grandpa gave up his family business in Hong Kong
تخلى جدي عن أعمال عائلته في هونج كونج
and came to Nanwu alone.
وجاء إلى نانوو وحده.
He's seen all kinds of people.
لقد رأى جميع أنواع الناس.
When your grandma was young
عندما كانت جدتك صغيرة
she must have been a great beauty.
لا بد أنها كانت ذات جمال عظيم.
And not only
وليس فقط
was she beautiful
هل كانت جميلة؟
but her education was also excellent.
ولكن تعليمها كان ممتازا أيضًا.
She was very well-known in Hong Kong's banking industry.
كانت مشهورة جدًا في مجال الصناعة المصرفية في هونغ كونغ.
All the household rules
جميع قواعد المنزل
were set by my grandma.
لقد تم وضعها من قبل جدتي.
My grandpa didn't dare to say a word.
لم يجرؤ جدي على قول كلمة واحدة.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Get out of the car.
اخرج من السيارة.
Wait for me a second.
انتظرني ثانية.
Let me prepare.
دعني أستعد.
Please close the window for me.
من فضلك أغلق النافذة بالنسبة لي.
What are you preparing for?
ماذا تستعد له؟
How's this?
كيف هذا؟
Remember
يتذكر
from the moment you step out of the car
من لحظة خروجك من السيارة
you're Wang Linlin.
أنت وانغ لينلين.
Got it.
فهمتها.
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
Wang Linlin.
وانغ لينلين.
It's not that I don't trust you
ليس الأمر أنني لا أثق بك
I'm just afraid you'll slip up.
أنا خائف فقط من أنك سوف تنزلق.
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
Wang Linlin.
وانغ لينلين.
Just forget about the past.
فقط انسي الماضي .
Today is the day to move forward.
اليوم هو اليوم للمضي قدما.
I'm 1.68 meters tall.
طولي 1.68 متر.
I weigh 90 jin.
وزني 90 جين.
I graduated from Changsha Media University.
لقد تخرجت من جامعة تشانغشا للإعلام.
I grew up in Hunan.
لقد نشأت في هونان.
After graduation, I came to Nanwu.
بعد التخرج، أتيت إلى نانوو.
We met
نحن مع
at a classmate's birthday party.
في حفل عيد ميلاد زميل في الفصل.
We've been together a year and a half
لقد كنا معًا لمدة عام ونصف
broken up twice.
انكسرت مرتين.
Once because you bought the wrong bag
مرة واحدة لأنك اشتريت الحقيبة الخطأ
and once because you overslept
ومرة واحدة لأنك نمت أكثر من اللازم
and didn't pick me up.
ولم يلتقطني.
The first breakup lasted two days
الانفصال الأول استمر يومين
and the second lasted three and a half days.
والثانية استمرت ثلاثة أيام ونصف.
Later, you bought the right bag
لاحقًا، اشتريت الحقيبة المناسبة
and I forgave you.
وسامحتك
Where did you get all this from?
من أين حصلت على كل هذا؟
I've been reading your posts on Weibo.
لقد قرأت مشاركاتك على Weibo.
I've also read your Moments
لقد قرأت لحظاتك أيضًا
through Dian's WeChat.
من خلال WeChat الخاص بديان.
Honestly, it's really hard to keep anything private
بصراحة، من الصعب حقًا الحفاظ على خصوصية أي شيء
these days.
في هذه الأيام.
Should I
هل يجب علي؟
block you guys from my Moments?
هل تريدون منعكم من لحظاتي؟
What?
ماذا؟
Miss Wen.
السيدة وين.
Morning.
صباح.
There's something for you.
هناك شيئا لك.
The lady who met you here last time
السيدة التي قابلتك هنا في المرة الأخيرة
dropped it off this morning.
أسقطته هذا الصباح.
Is she a relative of yours?
هل هي قريبة لك؟
Thanks, Uncle Zhang.
شكرا لك عم تشانغ.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Don't mention it.
لا تذكرها.
I've gained five pounds.
لقد اكتسبت خمسة جنيهات.
What are we having for lunch today?
ماذا سنتناول على الغداء اليوم؟
Today is the Lantern Festival.
اليوم هو مهرجان الفوانيس.
How about
ماذا عن
we go get some sweet dumplings?
هل نذهب للحصول على بعض الزلابية الحلوة؟
That sounds good.
فكرة جميلة.
Let's go to the tea shop first.
دعونا نذهب إلى محل الشاي أولاً.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
[Zhao Yuandong]
[تشاو يوان دونغ]
Jiang
جيانج
did you get the red envelope?
هل حصلت على الظرف الأحمر؟
I don't know
لا أعرف
where you are living in Nanwu.
أين تعيش في نانوو.
And you said you'd be working during the Spring Festival.
وقلت أنك ستعمل خلال مهرجان الربيع.
So, I sent it directly to your workplace.
لذا، أرسلته مباشرة إلى مكان عملك.
You probably think
ربما تعتقد
with WeChat red envelopes being so convenient
مع كون مظاريف WeChat الحمراء مريحة للغاية
why go through the trouble of delivering it?
لماذا نتحمل عناء تسليمه؟
I just prefer
انا فقط افضل
handing out the red envelope in person.
تسليم الظرف الأحمر شخصيا.
I always think about seeing you in person.
أنا أفكر دائمًا برؤيتك شخصيًا.
[To Wen Yifan]
[إلى وين ييفان]
[Jiang, wishing you great fortune and good health. - Mom]
[جيانغ، أتمنى لك حظًا سعيدًا وصحة جيدة. - أمي]
Jiang
جيانج
Happy New Year!
سنة جديدة سعيدة!
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
Go buy it yourself.
اذهب واشتريه بنفسك.
I don't want anything.
انا لا اريد شيئا
I just want you to get better soon.
أريد فقط أن تتحسن حالتك قريبًا.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Take it.
خذها.
It's the New Year.
إنها السنة الجديدة.
I want
أريد
to make a New Year wish.
لتحقيق أمنية العام الجديد.
May I?
ربما أنا؟
I want
أريد
to take you out for another day of fun.
لأخذك لقضاء يوم آخر من المرح.
Anywhere is fine.
أي مكان جيد.
Just one day.
يوم واحد فقط
You've already taken me to many places.
لقد أخذتني بالفعل إلى العديد من الأماكن.
Then, it's your turn to take us out.
ثم جاء دورك لتخرجنا.
When you get better
عندما تتحسن
I'll take you wherever you want to go.
سأأخذك إلى أي مكان تريد الذهاب إليه.
Okay.
تمام.
Ask your mom where she wants to go.
اسأل والدتك إلى أين تريد أن تذهب.
You need to make her happy.
يجب عليك أن تجعلها سعيدة.
[Jiang, wishing you great fortune and good health. - Mom]
[جيانغ، أتمنى لك حظًا سعيدًا وصحة جيدة. - أمي]
Hello
مرحبًا
Jiang.
جيانج.
I've received your red envelope.
لقد تلقيت ظرفتك الحمراء.
Thanks, Mom.
شكرا أمي.
I'm glad you received it.
أنا سعيد أنك تلقيته.
It's just a small token from me.
إنها مجرد هدية صغيرة مني.
Some day...
يوما ما...
when you're free
عندما تكون حرا
I'll come see you.
سوف آتي لرؤيتك.
Great.
عظيم.
I've been wanting to see you for a while.
لقد كنت أريد رؤيتك منذ فترة.
I'll make you something delicious.
سأعد لك شيئًا لذيذًا.
Let's do it this weekend.
دعونا نفعل ذلك في نهاية هذا الأسبوع.
What time do you usually finish work?
متى تنتهي من العمل عادة؟
How about you come over after work today?
ماذا عن أن تأتي بعد العمل اليوم؟
Are you in a rush?
هل أنت في عجلة من أمرك؟
Xin, come here.
تشين، تعال هنا.
My mom bought an extra bowl of sweet dumplings.
اشترت أمي وعاء إضافيًا من الزلابية الحلوة.
Let's eat together.
دعونا نأكل معا.
Coming.
آت.
Alright, see you after work today.
حسنًا، أراك بعد العمل اليوم.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
حسنًا، سأنتظرك.
See you at home.
نراكم في المنزل.
Oh my.
أوه يا إلهي.
Come on over.
تعالوا إلى هنا.
Linlin, right?
لينلين، أليس كذلك؟
Sit next to me.
اجلس بجانبي.
Okay.
تمام.
Uncle Ma
عمي ما
time to eat!
حان وقت الأكل!
Okay, I'm coming.
حسنًا، أنا قادم.
Ma, sit here.
أمي، اجلس هنا.
But what about him?
ولكن ماذا عنه؟
Just sit here.
فقط اجلس هنا .
I'll go help Grandpa.
سأذهب لمساعدة الجد.
Grandpa
الجد
let me help you.
دعني أساعدك.
was Grandma happy since she came back this time?
هل كانت الجدة سعيدة لأنها عادت هذه المرة؟
She's okay, I guess.
إنها بخير، على ما أعتقد.
But today
ولكن اليوم
you brought your girlfriend.
لقد أحضرت صديقتك.
She'll be happy.
ستكون سعيدة.
Really?
حقًا؟
But her expression seems a bit off.
لكن تعبيرها يبدو غريبا بعض الشيء.
Help me
ساعدني
serve the dishes, quickly.
قم بتقديم الأطباق بسرعة.
The dishes are ready.
الأطباق جاهزة.
Linlin
لينلين
you're in for a treat today.
أنت على موعد مع متعة كبيرة اليوم.
My cooking
طبخاتي
is top-notch in Nanwu!
هو الأفضل في نانوو!
Grandpa is amazing.
الجد مذهل.
Then I'll definitely enjoy this meal to the fullest!
ثم بالتأكيد سأستمتع بهذه الوجبة على أكمل وجه!
Good.
جيد.
An
أ
introduce her properly.
قدمها بشكل صحيح.
Grandpa, Grandma, this is Zhong Siqiao.
الجد، الجدة، هذا هو تشونج سي تشياو.
Zhong Siqiao?
تشونج سي تشياو؟
She's...
إنها...
I am...
أنا أكون...
living near a bridge
العيش بالقرب من الجسر
called Zhong Siqiao.
يُدعى تشونغ سي تشياو.
Exactly!
بالضبط!
My name is Wang Linlin.
اسمي وانغ لينلين.
- Right. - Just call me Linlin.
- صحيح. - فقط اتصل بي لينلين.
Ma
و
where's the Zhong Siqiao Bridge?
أين جسر تشونج سيتشياو؟
It's newly built!
لقد تم بناؤه حديثا!
- Right, newly built! - Newly built.
- صحيح، تم بناؤه حديثًا! - تم بناؤه حديثًا.
Newly built.
تم بناؤه حديثًا.
Miss Wang
السيدة وانغ
I've heard so much about you.
لقد سمعت الكثير عنك.
Grandpa
الجد
the dishes you made look so delicious.
الأطباق التي قمت بتحضيرها تبدو لذيذة جدًا.
It's a shame they're cold.
من العار أنهم باردون.
Let's eat quickly.
دعونا نأكل بسرعة.
Grandpa, please.
جدو من فضلك.
- Try it. - Come on.
- جربها. - هيا.
Quick, try it.
سريعًا، جربه.
This is my grandpa's specialty
هذا هو تخصص جدي
Kung Pao Shrimp.
روبيان كونغ باو.
This is white wine.
هذا هو النبيذ الأبيض.
I'll go get some tissues.
سأذهب للحصول على بعض المناديل.
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
Quick!
سريع!
Linlin is from Hunan.
لينلين من هونان.
Grandpa thinks Hunan folks love spicy food
يعتقد الجد أن أهل هونان يحبون الطعام الحار
so he added a lot of chili.
فأضاف الكثير من الفلفل الحار.
But you, being from Hunan, need to keep up!
لكنك، كونك من هونان، تحتاج إلى مواكبة ذلك!
Right.
يمين.
Here, cheers!
هنا، هتاف!
Move aside
تنحى جانبا
or it'll spill on you.
أو سينسكب عليك.
Grandma
الجدة
let me help you with the washing.
دعني أساعدك في الغسيل.
I'm good at washing cars.
أنا جيد في غسيل السيارات.
I'll help you.
سأساعدك.
Is it okay in this cold weather?
هل الأمر جيد في هذا الطقس البارد؟
It's fine. It's not cold.
إنه جيد، ليس باردًا.
Grandma
الجدة
these essential oils
هذه الزيوت العطرية
all have the function of refreshing.
جميعها لها وظيفة التحديث.
When get sleepy while driving
عندما تشعر بالنعاس أثناء القيادة
you can sniff them
يمكنك شمهم
apply them behind your ears, or on your neck.
ضعيها خلف أذنيك، أو على رقبتك.
It'll immediately lift your spirits.
سيؤدي ذلك إلى رفع معنوياتك على الفور.
You've studied this?
هل درست هذا؟
I often use them when I work night shifts.
أستخدمها غالبًا عندما أعمل في نوبات الليل.
You have my grandson as your personal ATM
لديك حفيدي كجهاز صرف آلي شخصي لك
why are you still working so hard?
لماذا لا تزال تعمل بجد؟
I know
أنا أعرف
you're not Wang Linlin.
أنت لست وانغ لينلين.
I just searched it on the map app.
لقد بحثت عنه للتو في تطبيق الخريطة.
There's no Zhong Siqiao Bridge
لا يوجد جسر تشونج سيتشياو
around Nanwu at all.
حول نانوو على الإطلاق.
Since Zhong Siqiao isn't a bridge
نظرًا لأن Zhong Siqiao ليس جسرًا
that must be your real name.
لا بد أن يكون هذا اسمك الحقيقي.
Grandma
الجدة
you're really too smart.
أنت ذكي جدًا حقًا.
All you old and young ones
كلكم كبار وصغار
don't tell me the truth.
لا تخبرني الحقيقة.
Grandma, don't be mad.
جدتي لا تغضبي.
We were wrong.
لقد كنا مخطئين.
But there's some good news.
ولكن هناك بعض الأخبار الجيدة.
Su Haoan has broken up
سو هاوان انفصلت
with the real Wang Linlin.
مع وانغ لينلين الحقيقي.
He asked me to pretend to be his girlfriend
لقد طلب مني أن أتظاهر بأنني صديقته
just to get you home for the New Year reunion.
فقط لإعادتك إلى المنزل للاحتفال بالعام الجديد.
I know what my grandson thought.
أنا أعلم ما كان يفكر فيه حفيدي.
I don't blame you.
انا لا ألومك.
But I am really curious.
ولكنني فضولي حقا.
As a young girl
كفتاة صغيرة
you can wash cars
يمكنك غسل السيارات
install things
تثبيت الأشياء
and aren't afraid to walk barefoot.
ولا يخافون من المشي حافي القدمين.
What do you do for a living?
ماذا تعمل لكسب عيشك؟
I just help out with everything
أنا فقط أساعد في كل شيء
fixing things
اصلاح الاشياء
queuing for tickets
الوقوف في طوابير للحصول على التذاكر
talking to the elderly
التحدث مع كبار السن
taking the elderly to see doctors, and more.
أخذ كبار السن لزيارة الأطباء، وأكثر من ذلك.
Is there this kind of job?
هل يوجد هذا النوع من العمل؟
Yeah.
نعم.
I even have a service app.
لدي أيضًا تطبيق خدمة.
There's a QR code on the business card.
هناك رمز الاستجابة السريعة (QR) على بطاقة العمل.
You can scan it and place an order.
يمكنك مسحه ضوئيًا ووضع طلب.
[Zhong Siqiao] If you ever need any help
[تشونج سي تشياو] إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي مساعدة في أي وقت
you can find me.
يمكنك أن تجدني.
Great.
عظيم.
I'll make sure my grandson
سأتأكد من حفيدي
gives you a good review.
يعطيك مراجعة جيدة.
Thank you, Grandma.
شكرا لك جدتي.
I'll continue helping you install it.
سأستمر في مساعدتك في تثبيته.
There's a massage chair left.
هناك كرسي تدليك متبقي.
Jiang, you're here!
جيانج، أنت هنا!
No need to change shoes. Just come in and sit.
لا داعي لتغيير الأحذية، فقط ادخل واجلس.
Why are you dressed so lightly?
لماذا ترتدي ملابس خفيفة هكذا؟
Isn't it cold outside?
أليس الجو باردًا في الخارج؟
This is for you.
هذا لك.
Sorry, I should've helped you with it.
عذرا، كان ينبغي علي أن أساعدك في ذلك.
Come in and sit.
تعال واجلس.
Come on, let's sit inside.
تعال، دعنا نجلس بالداخل.
Isn't it cold outside?
أليس الجو باردًا في الخارج؟
You're dressed too lightly.
أنت ترتدي ملابس خفيفة جدًا.
I'll go get you a cup of water.
سأذهب لأحضر لك كوبًا من الماء.
I didn't visit you before
لم أقم بزيارتك من قبل
because I didn't want
لأنني لم اكن اريد
to disturb you.
لإزعاجك.
I haven't seen you for so long.
لم أرك منذ فترة طويلة.
I'm a bit excited.
أنا متحمس قليلاً.
Here, drink some water.
هنا، اشرب بعض الماء.
Warm up your hands.
قم بتدفئة يديك.
Look at you
أنظر إليك
you've got so thin.
لقد أصبحت نحيفًا جدًا.
Haven't you been eating properly?
هل لم تأكل بشكل صحيح؟
If you want anything to eat, just tell me
إذا كنت تريد أي شيء لتأكله فقط أخبرني
I'll come over and make it for you.
سوف آتي وأصنعه لك.
No need.
لا حاجة.
I'm eating well.
أنا آكل جيدا.
Besides, I have a roommate. It's not convenient.
بالإضافة إلى ذلك، لدي زميل في السكن، وهذا ليس مناسبًا.
I still have things cooking in the kitchen.
لا يزال لدي أشياء للطبخ في المطبخ.
Knowing you were coming
معرفة أنك قادم
I made sweet dumplings specially for you.
لقد قمت بصنع الزلابية الحلوة خصيصًا لك.
You loved hot sweet dumplings when you were little.
لقد كنت تحب الزلابية الحلوة الساخنة عندما كنت صغيراً.
Today
اليوم
is the 15th day of the New Year.
هو اليوم الخامس عشر من العام الجديد.
This is when the family should reunite.
هذا هو الوقت الذي ينبغي أن تجتمع فيه العائلة.
Here.
هنا.
Hurry, eat it while it's hot.
اسرعي وتناوليه وهو ساخن.
Jiang
جيانج
you've grown up
لقد كبرت
and looked even prettier now.
وأصبحت تبدو أجمل الآن.
Why don't I see Uncle Zheng?
لماذا لا أرى العم تشنغ؟
And where's Zheng Kejia?
وأين تشنغ كيجيا؟
They
هم
took her grandma back to their hometown.
أخذت جدتها إلى مسقط رأسهم.
No wonder you insisted I come over today.
لا عجب أنك أصررت على أن آتي اليوم.
Mom.
أم.
Xin!
اطلب!
Why did you come down?
لماذا نزلت؟
Who is he?
من هو؟
I told you last time
لقد قلت لك المرة الماضية
I wanted to introduce someone to you.
أردت أن أقدم لك شخصًا ما.
This is him.
هذا هو.
He's the son of me and your Uncle Zheng.
إنه ابني وعمك تشنغ.
He's your real brother.
إنه أخوك الحقيقي.
His name is Zheng Kexin.
اسمه تشنغ كيكسين.
Mom, who is she?
أمي من هي؟
She's your sister, Jiang.
إنها أختك، جيانج.
She's also my child.
وهي طفلتي أيضاً.
She's your real sister.
إنها أختك الحقيقية.
Why didn't you mention her to me?
لماذا لم تذكرها لي؟
She didn't mention you to me either.
ولم تذكرك لي أيضًا.
Let me explain.
دعني أشرح لك.
I was quite old
لقد كنت عجوزا جدا
when I had him.
عندما كان عندي.
I even had a miscarriage before...
حتى أنني تعرضت للإجهاض من قبل...
Xin!
اطلب!
Who's this?
من هذا؟
Isn't that Jiang?
أليس هذا جيانج؟
How many years has it been since we last met?
كم سنة مرت منذ أن التقينا آخر مرة؟
Let me take a good look at you!
دعني ألقي عليك نظرة جيدة!
She was embarrassed to see you.
لقد شعرت بالخجل من رؤيتك.
What's embarrassing about that?
ما المحرج في ذلك؟
Jiang is not an outsider.
جيانج ليس غريبا.
Come on
تعال
let me take a good look at you.
دعني ألقي عليك نظرة جيدة.
Look at you
أنظر إليك
you're so ungrateful.
أنت جاحد جدًا.
You studied out of town for years
لقد درست خارج المدينة لسنوات
and never came back to see me
ولم يعود لرؤيتي مرة أخرى
honestly.
بصدق.
Why is she here?
لماذا هي هنا؟
It's a coincidence.
إنها مصادفة.
Your aunt just happened to come over.
لقد جاءت عمتك بالصدفة.
Jiang, don't act like that.
جيانج، لا تتصرف بهذه الطريقة.
Jiang
جيانج
what are you doing now?
ماذا تفعل الآن؟
By the way
بالمناسبة
my head hurt earlier, and my throat's sore.
كان رأسي يؤلمني في وقت سابق، وحلقي مؤلم.
Go get me some medicine.
اذهب واحضر لي بعض الدواء.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll get it for you.
سأحضره لك.
By the way
بالمناسبة
I have to tell you something.
أريد أن أخبرك بشيء.
Your cousin Wen Ming
ابن عمك وين مينغ
is getting married this year.
سيتزوج هذا العام.
Congratulations.
مبروك.
What's so great about it?
ما هو الشيء العظيم في هذا الأمر؟
They got the certificate
لقد حصلوا على الشهادة
but they haven't settled on the wedding house yet.
لكنهم لم يستقروا على بيت الزفاف بعد.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
You see
هل ترى
before
قبل
we took care of you for so long.
لقد اعتنينا بك لفترة طويلة.
You should at least help him.
ينبغي عليك مساعدته على الأقل.
After all, you're just a girl.
في نهاية المطاف، أنت مجرد فتاة.
You don't have many expenses.
ليس لديك الكثير من النفقات.
Right?
يمين؟
Aunt
عمة
I knew a lady lately.
لقد تعرفت على سيدة مؤخرًا.
She's very rich.
إنها غنية جدًا.
She's not very old
إنها ليست كبيرة في السن
two years younger than you.
أصغر منك بسنتين.
How about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
I could introduce her to Wen Ming.
أستطيع أن أقدمها إلى وين مينغ.
That way, you won't have to worry about the wedding house.
بهذه الطريقة، لن يكون عليك القلق بشأن بيت الزفاف.
What nonsense are you spouting?
ما هذا الهراء الذي تتفوه به؟
That's the only way I can talk to you.
هذه هي الطريقة الوحيدة التي أستطيع من خلالها التحدث معك.
If I knew you were such an ungrateful person
لو كنت أعلم أنك شخص جاحد إلى هذا الحد
I shouldn't have taken care of you back then!
لم يكن ينبغي لي أن أهتم بك في ذلك الوقت!
What's wrong, Jiang?
ما الأمر يا جيانج؟
I am going
وانا ذاهب
to cook for you.
لأطبخ لك.
I won't come here anymore.
لن أأتي إلى هنا بعد الآن.
This is the last time I'll be here.
هذه هي المرة الأخيرة التي سأكون فيها هنا.
All of you people...
جميعكم أيها الناس...
I don't want to see any of you again.
لا أريد رؤية أي منكم مرة أخرى.
I came for my dad's sake.
لقد جئت من أجل والدي.
Before my dad passed away, he told me
قبل أن يتوفى والدي، أخبرني
to take good care of you.
للعناية بك جيدا.
I have no choice but to follow his will.
ليس لدي خيار سوى اتباع إرادته.
Just consider it like I died with my dad.
فقط اعتبر الأمر كما لو أنني مت مع والدي.
You're talking nonsense.
أنت تتحدث هراء.
Dad didn't die.
أبي لم يمت.
Xin
اطلب
her dad isn't your dad.
والدها ليس والدك.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
♪Once again, I hear the farewell from that day♪
♪مرة أخرى، أسمع الوداع من ذلك اليوم♪
♪Tears fall as the memory replays...♪
♪تسقط الدموع عندما تتكرر الذكرى...♪
Be careful.
احرص.
♪Wishing for a better chapter ahead♪
♪أتمنى أن يكون الفصل القادم أفضل♪
♪The answers of time♪
♪إجابات الزمن♪
[I'm in the courtyard. Come join me?] ♪Should be handed in a bit late♪
[أنا في الفناء. هل يمكنك الانضمام إلي؟] ♪يجب تسليمها متأخرة قليلاً♪
♪The journey ahead should keep extending♪
♪الرحلة القادمة يجب أن تستمر في الامتداد♪
♪I fear you might be a little late♪
♪أخشى أن تتأخر قليلاً♪
♪Leaving me lost in the crowd...♪
♪تركني ضائعًا في الحشد...♪
It's the last day of the New Year holiday.
إنه اليوم الأخير من عطلة رأس السنة الجديدة.
I bought too many.
لقد اشتريت الكثير.
Help me light some?
ساعدني على إشعال بعض منها؟
♪Searching for you is destined to be a painful journey♪
♪البحث عنك مقدر له أن يكون رحلة مؤلمة♪
♪I'd rather you come a bit later♪
♪أفضّل أن تأتي متأخرًا قليلًا♪
♪The things we lose will be returned in the end...♪
"الأشياء التي نفقدها سوف تعود في النهاية..."
Jiang, do you want to try this?
جيانج، هل تريد تجربة هذا؟
Jiang, try it.
جيانج، جربه.
Light it up, come on.
أشعلها، هيا.
I'll light it.
سأشعلها.
Good.
جيد.
That's it?
هذا كل شيء؟
Here it goes.
وهنا يذهب.
Alright, let's watch it.
حسنًا، دعنا نشاهده.
Big fireworks.
الألعاب النارية الكبيرة.
Yeah.
نعم.
What shape is this?
ما هو هذا الشكل؟
A triangle.
مثلث.
♪Maybe forgetting some expectations...♪
♪ربما ننسى بعض التوقعات...♪
[Episode 7] [A Secret... that Can't be Kept]
[الحلقة 7] [سر... لا يمكن الاحتفاظ به]
Sir
سيد
[The story is not over yet...] did we make noise and bother you?
[القصة لم تنتهي بعد...] هل أحدثنا ضجيجًا وأزعجناك؟
We'll leave once these fireworks are done.
سوف نغادر بمجرد الانتهاء من هذه الألعاب النارية.
What time is it?
أي ساعة؟
Forget it. I want to go home now.
انسي الأمر، أريد العودة إلى المنزل الآن.
Alright, let's go.
حسناً، دعنا نذهب.
Wait a minute.
انتظر دقيقة.
How about selling these remaining ones
ماذا عن بيع تلك المتبقية؟
to me?
لي؟
Really?
حقًا؟
I'll pay you
سأدفع لك
double the price.
ضعف السعر.
That's great!
هذا رائع!
♪Even the strongest heart♪
♪حتى أقوى القلوب♪
♪Can waver♪
♪يمكن أن يتردد♪
♪And doubt its fire♪
♪و أشك في نارها♪
♪But you never lost faith in me♪
♪ولكنك لم تفقد الإيمان بي أبدًا♪
♪In every battle, every dream I chased♪
♪في كل معركة، في كل حلم سعيت لتحقيقه♪
♪There is meaning in every step I made♪
♪هناك معنى في كل خطوة اتخذتها♪
♪Through the storm, through the endless night♪
♪من خلال العاصفة، من خلال الليل الذي لا نهاية له♪
♪You were there, shining like a light♪
♪كنت هناك، تتألق مثل الضوء♪
♪Warm and bright♪
♪دافئ ومشرق♪
♪Standing right by my side♪
♪الوقوف بجانبي مباشرة♪
♪It was you, striding toward me through the storm♪
♪لقد كنت أنت، تتقدم نحوي عبر العاصفة♪
♪It was you, always cheering me on♪
♪لقد كنت أنت، الذي يشجعني دائمًا♪
♪The road is rough♪
♪الطريق وعر♪
♪The rain won't stop♪
♪المطر لن يتوقف♪
♪But with you here♪
♪ولكن معك هنا♪
♪I fear no dark♪
♪أنا لا أخاف من الظلام♪
♪Every thought, every memory is filled with you♪
♪كل فكرة وكل ذكرى مليئة بك♪
♪Marking our youth with every step we took♪
♪نترك بصمتنا على شبابنا مع كل خطوة نخطوها♪
♪When the downpour falls from the sky♪
♪عندما يهطل المطر من السماء♪
♪You're the one holding out an umbrella for me♪
♪أنت الشخص الذي يحمل لي المظلة♪
♪When the white dove brings the news♪
♪عندما تحمل الحمامة البيضاء الأخبار♪
♪You're the first I want to tell♪
♪أنت أول من أريد أن أخبره♪
♪I won't give up. I'll stay right here with you♪
♪لن أستسلم. سأبقى هنا معك♪
♪It was you, striding toward me through the storm♪
♪لقد كنت أنت، تتقدم نحوي عبر العاصفة♪
♪It was you, always cheering me on♪
♪لقد كنت أنت، الذي يشجعني دائمًا♪
♪The road is rough♪
♪الطريق وعر♪